Hello friends, in today's video I will
tell you how
you can get your first tech transaction
statement using ICICI's web portal. So friends,
watch the video till the end because every
step is important. If you miss it,
you might not be able to check your transaction.
So let's start. For this,
first of all you have to open your mobile's
google2 online,
after that you have to search it here.
After searching, you will already
see Fatak Pay Highway Toll Online
Electronic Toll here. You have to click on it.
After clicking, you will
see an interface like this. Here you will get an option
Assisting Customer. So you have to click here.
After clicking, you have to
scroll down a bit and here you will
get two options Individual Login and
Corporate Login. So you have to
click on Individual Login here.
After that, you will again get two options Login
either User Name or Login or Mobile Number. So
you have to click on the option below.
After that, you have to scroll down this page
and here you have to give your mobile number. The
mobile number will be given only by the person who  If it
is linked with your first, then you will
give your mobile number here and after that
you will have to fill a captcha here. This
captcha is visible here. If you do not understand this captcha,
then there is an option available here.
See, by clicking here you
can bring up another captcha as well. If you
understand the second one, then you have to fill it here. The
captcha has to be filled in the same way. If any
letter is small, then give it in small letters. If any
letter is capital, then give it in capital letters.
You have to fill it in the same way. So I will fill it.
After filling the captcha, you have to
click on Request for OTP.
After clicking, you have to
scroll down this page a little and here
you have to give that OTP. That OTP will be
sent to your mobile number.
You have to fill that OTP here. So I will
fill it. After filling the OTP,
tick on Remember Me here and
after that you have to log in here.
After logging in, you will get a
page like this, then here you will get an option
here, Do you  Want to convert to full
Kawasi, you
will click no here, after clicking no, two ads will come here,
cut and remove this and this,
after that you will see some such interface, then
you have to zoom a little here and
here you will get an option Statements
and Activity, you have to click here,
after clicking you will
see another option here Online Statement, so
you have to click here, after clicking
you have to click on the time period here below the online statement,
see what looks like a small arrow,
you have to click on it, after clicking
see here three options are visible today
weekly monthly now you can take out today's
statement as well as weekly, that
means you can take out the last one week
and monthly you can take out the statement up to the last one month
and you
can also bring it by entering the date here, you
will enter the date from to here, you can
take out anywhere up to the last one month here, you
cannot take out more than one month, you can take out less than one month
but you cannot take out more
and here you can also select monthly by clicking so
like  That
I click on monthly and
see here the date is selected after that
scroll a little to the left and
see here you will get an option Generate
Statement, you have to click on Generate Statement here
after that you have to zoom a little here again
after clicking on Generate Statement see here Save Statement
and after that Download Statement you have to
click on Download Statement here
so see after clicking on Download Statement
you will see your statement
and this is the downloaded file you will find in
your phone memory file in your member file
and see here you will
find it in PDF file so you
can zoom from here and check all the details
see here the
name of the toll you have passed through will also appear here
how much toll has been deducted you will get all the details from here
you will get it
from here and you will find
this file here in the file see you will find it in the
file here see you will find it
in the download file so
how did you like the video friends if you
liked the video then give it a like and a
comment and subscribe to the channel  Do
subscribe, so
friends, that's all for today, we'll meet again
in the next video, till then bye-bye
friends.